[EP12]
What do you mean?
Simply put,
someone wants to kill you.
Huh.
You don't believe me.
Why are you telling me this?
Don't you believe Chu Nanfeng
and think I destroyed the Su family?
Because I've already guessed
the Old Marshal is no longer alive,
And your uncle is impersonating him.
You are indeed very smart.
Yes.
My father is dead.
It was your father who killed him.
An eye for an eye.
Do you believe it?
My father killed your father.
The Su family is the right arm of the Ling family.
Destroying the Su family
means the Ling family will lose an arm.
Now I'm poisoned,
and someone in your mansion poisoned you.
Doesn't all this have anything to do with your father's death?
Don't you want us to work together to find out the truth?
I will find out the truth.
But I don't need you.
You still don't believe me.
But I will prove to you
that I am your most trustworthy partner.
My Lady,
this is the freshly heated milk.
Have a good rest.
My Lady,
have you noticed
that the servants in the mansion
have been changing frequently lately?
Auntie Wang, who was cleaning the front yard yesterday,
is nowhere to be seen today.
Even
the personal maids around Second Concubine
have been replaced with new faces.
Who arranged this?
I don't know.
Recently,
everyone is in danger.
The servants dare not speak much.
Yesterday, when I went to the kitchen,
I heard two old ladies talking
that the cenotaph is not right.
And they disappeared yesterday afternoon.
I see.
You can go now.
[It seems that Ling Shenxing]
[pretends not to believe me,]
[but his actions are honest.]
[He has already started investigating]
[who is poisoning.]
[Why did Ling Shenxing suddenly change my maid?]
[Could it be...]
Second Concubine,
you've been busy all day
and haven't even had a sip of hot tea.
Please take a rest.
I'll get you a bowl of bird's nest soup.
It's fine.
No need.
You should get some rest too.
This was just given to me
by a gentleman to give to you.
Remember,
no one can enter
without my permission.
Yes, ma'am.
Sir?
[Who could it be?]
[Who wrote that note?]
[He must know something.]
[If Ling Shenxing finds out anything,]
[what will happen]
[to the baby?]
[I need to make other plans.]
Someone!
Willow.
Madam,
the midwife said Second Concubine is having a difficult labor.
They are at their wits' end.
It's okay, it should be fine.
Jinrou, Jinrou said she knows traditional Chinese medicine.
She should be fine.
Please,
save my child.
Concubine,
don't worry,
I'm here.
She's been in pain all night.
Please, Miss Ye,
save her.
She's bleeding heavily.
We need a lot of hot water.
Go get it.
Now!
Jinrou,
if you can pull through this
and save the Ling family's heir,
I'll make a decision.
Tomorrow I'll announce to the whole city
that you have done a great service to us.
I'll marry you into the Ling residence
as the young madam.
Madam,
don't worry.
I'll try my best.
Su Muwan,
the Second Concubine is in danger.
Don't you want to save her?
Hang in there!
Save her!
Do you have the ability to do that?
Don't forget
the last patient died in the end.
Was that her fault?
Don't listen to her.
Su Muwan,
you are a doctor.
I didn't know
you were so close to her.
Even if you have a grudge,
two lives are at stake.
As a human being,
I hope the baby is born safely.
This is the bottom line.
Her condition is not good.
She's bleeding.
Young Marshal,
the Old Madam wants to see you.
I'll go with you.
Okay.
Come here.
Madam.
Just say it.
Second Madame's bleeding doesn't stop.
Three doctors have been invited, but it doesn't work.
We've tried acupuncture and medicine.
If it goes on like this,
the baby may be lost.
And her pulse is getting weaker.
Oh my!
What should we do?
Go to the hospital
and see a western doctor.
No way!
The hospital is full of people
from all walks of life.
How could a Ling family's concubine go there
and be seen naked?
What if she gets
an infectious disease?
If the news gets out,
what will happen
to our reputation?
Ling Shenxing,
are you tired of being disciplined?
You disregard our family rules!
The Second Concubine fainted.
Her pulse is barely detectable.
Oh my!
What should we do?
Amitabha!
Please bless us!
Young Marshal,
the doctor went out to see patients.
He won't be back for four hours.
Grandma,
let's go to the hospital.
I'll take full responsibility.
Can you?
What kind of place is the hospital?
It's a mixed bag.
There are no decent female doctors,
only male doctors.
Do you want your second aunt
to be seen by a male doctor?
Do you want your
unborn brother to lose dignity?
You unfilial and disloyal thing!
Do you even have your father in your eyes?
You're unworthy of being a son!
Guards!
Take him to the ancestral tablets
and make him kneel!
Sister, I believe in you.
I'll save...